lyricsmint.com 2019-07-28

# Privacy & Cookie Policy

Lyricsmint.com (“ **LyricsMINT** “) operates lyricsMINT.com and may operate other websites. It is LyricsMINT’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, LyricsMINT collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. LyricsMINT’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how LyricsMINT’s visitors use its website. From time to time, LyricsMINT may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to LyricsMINT’s websites choose to interact with LyricsMINT in ways that require LyricsMINT to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that LyricsMINT gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.

## Aggregated Statistics

LyricsMINT may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. LyricsMINT may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, LyricsMINT does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

LyricsMINT discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on LyricsMINT’s behalf or to provide services available at LyricsMINT’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using LyricsMINT’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. LyricsMINT will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, LyricsMINT discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when LyricsMINT believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of LyricsMINT, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an LyricsMINT website and have supplied your email address, LyricsMINT may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with LyricsMINT and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. LyricsMINT takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. LyricsMINT uses cookies to help LyricsMINT identify and track visitors, their usage of LyricsMINT website, and their website access preferences. LyricsMINT visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using LyricsMINT’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of LyricsMINT’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

We use various third-party tools and services for advertising and analytics. These include Google Adsense, Google Analytics, Facebook Commenting and Social Share Widgets. We use Cloudflare as CDN which also uses its cookies and processes content of our website to improve performance, security and provide analytics to serve our visitors better.

Please read following terms to learn how various third parties collect and use the information:

  * [How Google uses information from sites or apps that use our services](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)

## Business Transfers

If LyricsMINT, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that LyricsMINT goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of LyricsMINT may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by LyricsMINT and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## How can users manage or opt out of cookies?

Some people find the idea of a website storing information on their device a little intrusive, in particular when the information is stored and used by a third party. For example, you may object to being served advertising which is targeted to your interests based on your browsing history. If you would prefer to opt out of cookies, it is possible to control cookies by following the steps below, however you should be aware that you might lose some features and functionality of the website if you do so.

Cookies, including those which have already been set, can be deleted from your hard drive. You can also change the preferences/settings in your web browser to control cookies. Some internet browsers have a ‘Do Not Track or ‘DNT’ setting; this sends a signal to websites asking them not to track your browsing. The following links may be helpful:

In some cases, you can choose to accept cookies from the primary site, but block them from third parties. In others, you can block cookies from specific advertisers, or clear out all cookies. Deleting or blocking cookies may reduce functionality of the site. To learn more about how to reject cookies, visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> or go to the help menu within your internet browser. If you experience any problems having deleted cookies, you should contact the supplier of your web browser.

For more information about third party cookies generated by advertisers please visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Please be aware that these are third party websites and LyricsMint does not accept any liability for the instructions given on these sites.

You can find out how to decline targeting and behavioural advertising cookies by visiting: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/> [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

## Privacy Policy Changes

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/lyricsmint.com).  

Although most changes are likely to be minor, LyricsMINT may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in LyricsMINT’s sole discretion. LyricsMINT encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a lyricsMINT.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
